[RAJESH SNEEZES]
(Sheldon:)-Hold.
-What?
(Sheldon:)Explain your sneeze.
(Raj:)-I'm sorry?
-Do you have allergies?
(Raj:)-No.
-Too much pepper on your salad?
(Raj:)-I don't put pepper on salads.
-I've heard enough. Sit over there.
Come on, I don't wanna sit by myself.
(Sheldon:)That's what Typhoid Mary said.
Clearly, her friends buckled.
(Raj:)Guys, help me.
(Howard:)-Sheldon, come on.
-Yeah, it's just one sneeze.
[RAJESH SNEEZES]
(Leonard:)-You're on your own.
-See you, buddy.
(Sheldon:)Oh, Leonard, I have something for you.
(Sheldon:)Per our roommate agreement,
this is your 24-hour notice...
(Sheldon:)...that I will be having
a non-related female...
(Sheldon:)...spending two nights
in our apartment.
(Leonard:)When you say non-related female,
you still mean human, right?
Well, of course.
Pets are banned by the agreement,
with the exception of service animals...
(Sheldon:)...such as Seeing Eye dogs
and, one day...
...cybernetically enhanced
helper monkeys.
(Howard:)Are you planning
on kidnapping a woman?